<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TailorSmart</string>

    <string name="open_drawer">Open</string>
    <string name="close_drawer">Close</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="notification_channel_name">notification</string>
    <string name="about_us">While our busy lifestyles today might not allow us the time to indulge in tailoring services, our love for custom made clothes has not diminished. This is where TailorSmart.in strives to bridge the gap. We are a service company specialising in Made to Measure items like clothing, shoes etc. Providing you with “Tailor at Home” service with just a click of a few buttons, we hope we provide you an experience you can keep coming back to. Never again should the hassles of visiting a tailor hamper you from a good fitted outfit – be it business wear, casual wear, Indian ethnic clothes, even shoes!.\n\nTailorSmart.in brings to you the 100-year old legacy of skilled craftsmen whose simple endeavour is to ensure the best of fit for you. Now you can access the best of quality stitching and skilled craftsmanship at your door-step with TailorSmart.in. Book an appointment today to witness the seamless experience and revel in the new found ease of tailoring.\n\nTailorSmart.in draws its roots from a family-run business that holds close to a 100 years of rich history. The business grew and thrived through decades, tailoring and serving the audiences in Pune. Pravin, a law graduate turned owner of the business took it to new heights, adding readymade and ethnic wear to its expertise.\n\nIn 2008, Pravin, along with an old friend, Joy conceptualized ‘Tailor at your doorstep’ service for enterprises. They incorporated a firm (which was later dissolved ) on this model. While a brilliant business model, it lacked a digital platform which would usher in the ease of selecting a fabric online. On their journey, Joy and Pravin met Pritam, a loyal customer and influencer who brought this idea on the table and joined them on the dream ride which is today, TailorSmart.in.\n\nAt TailorSmart, we envision ourselves as more than online tailoring service. We are striving to be a platform for bringing together and organizing the tailor community as well as the designer community. Read more about our initiatives below:\n\n<b>Refer a Tailor</b> – Refer your nearby tailor to TailorSmart and make a difference to his life.\n<b>Budding Designers</b> – Platform for young budding designers to showcase their designs on TailorSmart and earn a living.</string>
    <string name="joy_info">A professional with over 15 years of experience in IT and telecom sector, Joy ventured out into entrepreneurship with an old friend, Pravin, conceptualizing ‘Tailor at your doorstep’ service.</string>
    <string name="pritam_info">An alumnus of Indian Institute of Management, Ahmedabad ( MDP) and a Master Degree in management from Pune University, Pritam has 15+ years of experience in the telecom and FMCG sector with exposure in india and international markets. TailorSmart is Pritam’s venture into the entrepreneurial world.</string>
    <string name="pravin_info">A Law Graduate with 2 year practice in the field of Anti Corruption, Pravin’s life took a sharp turn when he was entrusted to choose between law and a 100 year old family run tailoring and garment business. Inheriting a vast legacy of craftsmen and trusted and loyal customers, Pravin took the business to new heights venturing from mens tailoring to readymade to ethnic wear while fine tuning the company’s core competence of tailoring and fabrics.\nWith TailorSmart.in, Pravin wishes to cater to the new breed of clientele who do not have the time to visit a tailor and who are used to gratification of most or all of their day-to-day requirements digitally..</string>
    <string name="contact_us_address">\"Tailorsmart\" , 1st floor, WeWorks, next to Seasons Mall, Magarpatta , Pune.</string>
    <string name="terms_amp_conditions"><![CDATA[Terms & Conditions]]></string>
</resources>
